{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "(6, -7.5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((-4 + 16)/2 , (10 - 25)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (-4, 10) and Point B (16, -25): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(15.5, -18)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((9 + 22)/2 , (-16 - 20)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (9, -16) and Point B (22, -20): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√2", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((-6 + 5)^2 + (6 - 5)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (-6, 6) to Point B (-5, 5): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-16, 3)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((-11 - 21)/2 , (22 - 16)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (-11, 22) and Point B (-21, -16): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-4, -6.5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((3 - 11)/2 , (-7 - 6)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (3, -7) and Point B (-11, -6): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√148", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((2 - 4)^2 + (9 + 3)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (2, 9) to Point B (4, -3): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√197", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((9 + 5)^2 + (-5 + 6)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (9, -5) to Point B (-5, -6): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(1, 21)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((-4 + 6)/2 , (25 + 17)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (-4, 25) and Point B (6, 17): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√157", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((-2 - 4)^2 + (-10 - 1)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (-2, -10) to Point B (4, 1): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√37", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((-1 + 2)^2 + (-5 - 1)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (-1, -5) to Point B (-2, 1): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(14.5, 6)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((23 + 6)/2 , (24 - 12)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (23, 24) and Point B (6, -12): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(9.5, -22)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((7 + 12)/2 , (-19 - 25)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (7, -19) and Point B (12, -25): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "13", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((8 + 5)^2 + (9 - 9)^2)\n√169", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (8, 9) to Point B (-5, 9): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√185", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((4 + 7)^2 + (9 - 1)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (4, 9) to Point B (-7, 1): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(18.5, 7)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((16 + 21)/2 , (9 + 5)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (16, 9) and Point B (21, 5): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√61", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((3 - 9)^2 + (8 - 3)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (3, 8) to Point B (9, 3): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√73", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((-10 + 2)^2 + (4 - 7)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (-10, 4) to Point B (-2, 7): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(17.5, -12)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((10 + 25)/2 , (-8 - 16)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (10, -8) and Point B (25, -16): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√65", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((5 - 9)^2 + (1 + 6)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (5, 1) to Point B (9, -6): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(17.5, -1.5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((16 + 19)/2 , (11 - 14)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (16, 11) and Point B (19, -14): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(8, -6.5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((9 + 7)/2 , (-25 + 12)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (9, -25) and Point B (7, 12): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√8", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((-5 + 3)^2 + (3 - 5)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (-5, 3) to Point B (-3, 5): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(15.5, 9.5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((23 + 8)/2 , (3 + 16)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (23, 3) and Point B (8, 16): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((3 - 3)^2 + (2 - 8)^2)\n√36", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (3, 2) to Point B (3, 8): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√221", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((3 - 8)^2 + (10 + 4)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (3, 10) to Point B (8, -4): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4, 13)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((-7 + 15)/2 , (18 + 8)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (-7, 18) and Point B (15, 8): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-6, -5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((3 - 15)/2 , (-19 + 9)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (3, -19) and Point B (-15, 9): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2.5, 13)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((-1 + 6)/2 , (3 + 23)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (-1, 3) and Point B (6, 23): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(14.5, 5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((22 + 7)/2 , (3 + 7)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (22, 3) and Point B (7, 7): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-4, 3.5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((-21 + 13)/2 , (-12 + 19)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (-21, -12) and Point B (13, 19): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(9.5, -7)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((9 + 10)/2 , (2 - 16)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (9, 2) and Point B (10, -16): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "17", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((-6 - 9)^2 + (1 - 9)^2)\n√289", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (-6, 1) to Point B (9, 9): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((-5 + 8)^2 + (8 - 8)^2)\n√9", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (-5, 8) to Point B (-8, 8): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√245", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((-8 - 6)^2 + (1 - 8)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (-8, 1) to Point B (6, 8): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√113", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((1 - 9)^2 + (2 + 5)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (1, 2) to Point B (9, -5): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-7.5, 2.5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((-19 + 4)/2 , (21 - 16)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (-19, 21) and Point B (4, -16): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√13", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((2 + 1)^2 + (4 - 6)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (2, 4) to Point B (-1, 6): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√85", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((10 - 4)^2 + (10 - 3)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (10, 10) to Point B (4, 3): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√13", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((6 - 9)^2 + (6 - 8)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (6, 6) to Point B (9, 8): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-10.5, 2)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((-22 + 1)/2 , (-12 + 16)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (-22, -12) and Point B (1, 16): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√40", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((1 - 3)^2 + (4 + 2)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (1, 4) to Point B (3, -2): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(1, -7)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((-22 + 24)/2 , (-12 - 2)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (-22, -12) and Point B (24, -2): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√10", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((7 - 8)^2 + (8 - 5)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (7, 8) to Point B (8, 5): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√265", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((5 - 2)^2 + (9 + 7)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (5, 9) to Point B (2, -7): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√2", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((2 - 1)^2 + (3 - 4)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (2, 3) to Point B (1, 4): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((-2 + 7)^2 + (9 - 9)^2)\n√25", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (-2, 9) to Point B (-7, 9): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6.5, 9)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((-8 + 21)/2 , (-1 + 19)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (-8, -1) and Point B (21, 19): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√65", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((5 - 1)^2 + (10 - 3)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (5, 10) to Point B (1, 3): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-18, 1.5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((-23 - 13)/2 , (-19 + 22)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (-23, -19) and Point B (-13, 22): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√157", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((-5 - 6)^2 + (1 - 7)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (-5, 1) to Point B (6, 7): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((9 - 9)^2 + (7 - 10)^2)\n√9", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (9, 7) to Point B (9, 10): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2.5, 13)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((17 - 12)/2 , (5 + 21)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (17, 5) and Point B (-12, 21): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√130", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((-8 - 3)^2 + (6 - 3)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (-8, 6) to Point B (3, 3): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√325", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((4 + 6)^2 + (10 + 5)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (4, 10) to Point B (-6, -5): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(14.5, -2.5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((20 + 9)/2 , (-11 + 6)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (20, -11) and Point B (9, 6): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-1.5, 17.5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((-4 + 1)/2 , (17 + 18)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (-4, 17) and Point B (1, 18): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√40", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((4 - 6)^2 + (5 + 1)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (4, 5) to Point B (6, -1): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(0, -14)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((8 - 8)/2 , (-5 - 23)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (8, -5) and Point B (-8, -23): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(12.5, 13.5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((12 + 13)/2 , (14 + 13)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (12, 14) and Point B (13, 13): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(9, 3.5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((10 + 8)/2 , (20 - 13)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (10, 20) and Point B (8, -13): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((1 + 10)^2 + (1 - 1)^2)\n√121", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (1, 1) to Point B (-10, 1): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4.5, 8)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((22 - 13)/2 , (12 + 4)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (22, 12) and Point B (-13, 4): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-11, 16)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((1 - 23)/2 , (18 + 14)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (1, 18) and Point B (-23, 14): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√130", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((-10 + 1)^2 + (3 - 10)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (-10, 3) to Point B (-1, 10): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√17", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((7 - 6)^2 + (-4 + 8)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (7, -4) to Point B (6, -8): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(1.5, 0)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((-5 + 8)/2 , (-21 + 21)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (-5, -21) and Point B (8, 21): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(18, -7)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((11 + 25)/2 , (-18 + 4)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (11, -18) and Point B (25, 4): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(7.5, -7)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((-9 + 24)/2 , (5 - 19)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (-9, 5) and Point B (24, -19): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√58", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((5 - 8)^2 + (-1 - 6)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (5, -1) to Point B (8, 6): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-6.5, 11)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((6 - 19)/2 , (17 + 5)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (6, 17) and Point B (-19, 5): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√328", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((-8 - 10)^2 + (1 - 3)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (-8, 1) to Point B (10, 3): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√130", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((5 + 4)^2 + (3 + 4)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (5, 3) to Point B (-4, -4): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√82", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((3 + 6)^2 + (-9 + 10)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (3, -9) to Point B (-6, -10): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-13.5, 16.5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((-3 - 24)/2 , (12 + 21)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (-3, 12) and Point B (-24, 21): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(13, 2)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((2 + 24)/2 , (-13 + 17)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (2, -13) and Point B (24, 17): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-5, 1)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((-20 + 10)/2 , (-1 + 3)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (-20, -1) and Point B (10, 3): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√85", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((-8 - 1)^2 + (-4 + 2)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (-8, -4) to Point B (1, -2): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6, 4.5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((-7 + 19)/2 , (22 - 13)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (-7, 22) and Point B (19, -13): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√421", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((-4 - 10)^2 + (9 + 6)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (-4, 9) to Point B (10, -6): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6, 9)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((3 + 9)/2 , (1 + 17)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (3, 1) and Point B (9, 17): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(11.5, 9.5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((18 + 5)/2 , (10 + 9)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (18, 10) and Point B (5, 9): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6, -5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((-13 + 25)/2 , (-11 + 1)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (-13, -11) and Point B (25, 1): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-19.5, 10.5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((-15 - 24)/2 , (3 + 18)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (-15, 3) and Point B (-24, 18): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√328", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((8 + 10)^2 + (-1 + 3)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (8, -1) to Point B (-10, -3): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2.5, 5.5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((3 + 2)/2 , (-11 + 22)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (3, -11) and Point B (2, 22): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(11.5, 10)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((11 + 12)/2 , (23 - 3)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (11, 23) and Point B (12, -3): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√37", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((9 - 10)^2 + (-1 + 7)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (9, -1) to Point B (10, -7): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√292", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((-10 - 6)^2 + (5 + 1)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (-10, 5) to Point B (6, -1): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√128", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((2 + 6)^2 + (9 - 1)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (2, 9) to Point B (-6, 1): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√229", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((10 + 5)^2 + (6 - 4)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (10, 6) to Point B (-5, 4): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√13", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((-2 - 1)^2 + (-5 + 3)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (-2, -5) to Point B (1, -3): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((7 - 4)^2 + (-9 + 9)^2)\n√9", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (7, -9) to Point B (4, -9): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(17.5, -1)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((19 + 16)/2 , (3 - 5)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (19, 3) and Point B (16, -5): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(10.5, 0)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((5 + 16)/2 , (6 - 6)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (5, 6) and Point B (16, -6): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4, 10.5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((13 - 5)/2 , (13 + 8)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (13, 13) and Point B (-5, 8): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(11.5, -3)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((5 + 18)/2 , (-22 + 16)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (5, -22) and Point B (18, 16): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√50", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((9 - 10)^2 + (-2 - 5)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (9, -2) to Point B (10, 5): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√50", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((9 - 10)^2 + (3 - 10)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (9, 3) to Point B (10, 10): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√106", "explanation": "Plug the points into the distance formula\n√((-7 + 2)^2 + (10 - 1)^2)\n", "question": "Find the distance from \n Point A (-7, 10) to Point B (-2, 1): ", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(12.5, 4.5)", "explanation": "Plug the points into the midpoint formula\n((16 + 9)/2 , (6 + 3)/2)\nSimplify for the answer.", "prompt": "(x, y) \u003d", "question": "Find the midpoint of Point A \n (16, 6) and Point B (9, 3): ", "type": "text"}
]}